A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Soviet Studies, Record Group 3, Series 6 FA1486
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Programs and Development, 1980-1994; 1
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Requests, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 217)
    Responses to funding requests for 1991 workshop and other correspondence. Includes 1989 workshop report.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Proposal for 1988-1990, 1987 October (Box 25, Folder 218)
    Proposal (to the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation?) for support of summer workshops in 1988-1990.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Proposal for 1991-1992, 1989 December (Box 25, Folder 219)
    Proposal to the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation for support of summer workshops in 1991-1992.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Proposal for 1991-1992, 1990 February (Box 25, Folder 220)
    Proposal (to the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation?) for support of summer workshops in 1991-1992.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding - Draft Proposals to the Bradley Foundation, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 221)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Proposal for 1991-1992, 1990 September (Box 25, Folder 222)
    Proposal to the Bradley Foundation for support of summer workshops in 1991-1992.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Proposal to the Ford Foundation for 1991, 1990 October (Box 25, Folder 223)
    For support of 1991 summer workshop.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Proposal to the Sarah Scaife Foundation for 1991, 1990 December (Box 25, Folder 224)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy - Meeting of U.S. and Soviet International Relations Theorists, 1981-1983 January (Box 25, Folder 225)
    Report on first meeting, Moscow, January 24-26, 1983.
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Membership, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 226)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Meeting, 1983 November 11 (Box 25, Folder 227)
    First meeting. Includes materials from the Soviet-American Parallel Studies Program of the UNA-USA, 1980-1981.
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Dual Seminar on Soviet Foreign Policy Study, 1984 February 3-4 (Box 25, Folder 228)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Dual Seminar on Soviet Foreign Policy Study, 1984 March 2-3 (Box 25, Folder 229)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Dual Seminar on Soviet Foreign Policy Study - Notes, 1984 February-March (Box 25, Folder 230)
    Notes on February 3-4 and March 2-3 meetings.
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Dual Seminar on Soviet Foreign Policy Study - Agenda and Readings, 1984 May 17-18 (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Dual Seminar on Soviet Foreign Policy Study - Notes, 1984 May 17-18 (Box 26, Folder 232)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Dual Competency Seminar (2017:017:002 - 2017:017:008), 1984?; Seven audio cassette tapes. (Box 26, Folder 232)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Dual Seminar on Soviet Foreign Policy Study - Syllabi and Reading Lists, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 233-235)
    Course syllabi from programs at U.S. universities.
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Guide to University-Based Graduate Training Programs in Soviet International Behavior (Correspondence), 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 236)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Guide to University-Based Graduate Training Programs in Soviet International Behavior (Manuscript Drafts), 1985 March (Box 26, Folder 237)
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Guide to University-Based Graduate Training Programs in Soviet International Behavior (Revisions and Updates), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 238)
    Published January 1986.
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Jack Snyder, New Methods and Old Virtues in the Study of Soviet Foreign Policy, 1986 June (Box 27, Folder 239)
    Paper.
  - JCSS - Foreign Policy Subcommittee - Proposed "State of the Art" Volume, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 240)
    Proposal for conferences and publication on the state of Soviet Foreign Policy studies.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - Program and Membership, 1983-1988 (Box 27, Folder 241)
    Program proposals and membership. Includes memo for January 1984 meeting.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - Meeting, 1984 January 13 (Box 27, Folder 242)
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - Meeting, 1984 March 16 (Box 27, Folder 243)
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - Survey of Courses on Soviet History, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 244)
    Correspondence, proposals, request for syllabi and reading lists.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - National Seminar on Soviet Social History - Proposal and Award, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 245)
    Funding proposal to SSRC.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - National Seminar on Soviet Social History - The Civil War, 1984 October 27-28, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 246)
    Conference held at the University of Pennsylvania. Includes 1988 correspondence concerning publication of the proceedings.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - National Seminar on Soviet Social History - The Civil War (Papers), 1984 October 27-28 (Box 27, Folder 247-249)
    Conference held at the University of Pennsylvania.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - Handbook of Sources on Soviet Social History, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 250)
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - New Economic Policy (NEP) Conference Planning Meeting, 1985 September 14 (Box 28, Folder 251)
    Planning for National Seminar on Culture and Society in NEP Russia, October 1986.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - National Seminar on Soviet Social History - Culture and Society in NEP Russia (1986 October 2-5), 1985-1989 (Box 28, Folder 252)
    New Economic Policy (NEP), 1921-1928. Conference held at Indiana University.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - Meeting, 1987 April 17 (Box 28, Folder 253)
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - Meeting, 1988 March 5 (Box 28, Folder 254)
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - National Seminar on Soviet Social History - 1930s (Industrialization and Change), 1984-1988 (Box 28, Folder 255)
    Correspondence and Planning. Conference held at University of Michigan.
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - National Seminar on Soviet Social History - 1930s (Industrialization and Change) - Papers, 1988 April 22-24 (Box 28, Folder 256-258)
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - National Seminar on Soviet Social History - 1930s (Industrialization and Change) - Papers, 1988 April 22-24 (Box 29, Folder 259)
  - JCSS - History Subcommittee - Kendall Bailes Research Assistant, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 260)
    Research assistance for Bailes's biography of V. I. Vernadsky (Science and Russian Culture in an Age of Revolutions).
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Membership and Vitae, 1985-1988 (Box 29, Folder 261)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 262)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Meeting, 1983 December (Box 29, Folder 263)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Meeting, 1985 March (Box 29, Folder 264)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Meeting, 1986 May (Box 29, Folder 265)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Meeting, 1986 September (Box 29, Folder 266)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Meeting, 1987 May (Box 29, Folder 267)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Meeting, 1988 May (Box 29, Folder 268)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 269)
    Memo on the proposed dismissal of the subcommittee.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - World War II and Soviet Union Project, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 270)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - World War II Conference - Planning Meeting, 1986 September (Box 30, Folder 271)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - World War II Conference - Planning and Cancellation, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 272)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Soviet Handbook Project - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 273)
    Proposed Handbook of Sovietology.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Soviet Handbook Project - Meeting, 1985 June (Box 30, Folder 274)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Hauslohner Proposal (Political Control of the Soviet Economy Workshop), 1986-1988 (Box 30, Folder 275)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Political Control of the Soviet Economy Workshop - Papers, 1989 March 16-19 (Box 30, Folder 276-277)
    Workshop held at Yale University.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee -Soviet Studies Survey Form, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 278)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Soviet Domestic Politics Workshop Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 279)
    Correspondence and draft proposal, May 1987, for support of summer workshops in 1988 and 1989.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Soviet Domestic Politics Workshop Proposal, 1987 August (Box 30, Folder 280)
    Proposal submitted to the Carnegie Corporation for support of summer workshops in 1988 and 1989.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Planning, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 281)
    First Annual Summer Workshop, 1988 June 5-17, University of Toronto.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Participants, 1988 June 5-17 (Box 31, Folder 282)
    First Annual Summer Workshop, University of Toronto.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Papers, 1988 June 5-17 (Box 31, Folder 283-285)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Report, 1988 June 5-17 (Box 31, Folder 286)
    Includes Includes participants' responses to evaluation questionnaire.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Soviet Domestic Politics Workshops Proposal, 1989 April (Box 31, Folder 287)
    From Crisis to Opportunity - A Proposal for Two Further Workshops on Soviet Domestic Politics. For funding of summer workshops 3-4, in 1990 and 1991.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Soviet Domestic Politics Workshop Reader (in Russian), 1989 June (Box 31, Folder 288)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Papers (folder 1 of 4), 1989 June 5-16 (Box 31, Folder 289)
    Second workshop, University of Toronto.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Papers, 1989 June 5-16 (Box 32, Folder 290-292)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Final Report on the Summer Workshops on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society, 1989 August (Box 32, Folder 293)
    Report focuses on the second workshop in June 1989. Includes participant questionnaire.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Third Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Planning and Arrangements, 1990 June 10-22 (Box 32, Folder 294)
    University of Toronto.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Third Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Report, 1990 June 10-22 (Box 32, Folder 295)
    University of Toronto. Report submitted to the Carnegie Corporation in December 1990. Includes participant questionnaire.
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Fourth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - General, 1991 June 9-21 (Box 32, Folder 296)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Fourth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Papers (Folder 1 of 4), 1991 June 9-21 (Box 32, Folder 297)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Fourth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Papers, 1991 June 9-21 (Box 33, Folder 298-300)
  - JCSS - Domestic Politics Subcommittee - Fourth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Report, 1991 June 9-21 (Box 33, Folder 301)
    Report dated September 1991. Includes participant questionnaire.
  - JCSSS - Fifth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Schedule, Faculty, Participants, 1992 June 7-19 (Box 33, Folder 302)
  - JCSSS - Fifth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Papers, 1992 June 7-19 (Box 33, Folder 303)
  - JCSSS - Fifth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Readings, 1992 June 7-19 (Box 33, Folder 304)
  - JCSSS - Fifth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Readings, 1992 June 7-19 (Box 34, Folder 305)
  - JCSSS - Fifth Annual Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Evaluations, 1992 June 7-19 (Box 34, Folder 306)
  - JCSSS - Sixth Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - General, 1993 June 6-18 (Box 34, Folder 307)
  - JCSSS - Sixth Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Papers, 1993 June 6-18 (Box 34, Folder 308-311)
  - JCSSS - Sixth Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Faculty Papers, 1993 June 6-18 (Box 34, Folder 312-313)
  - JCSSS - Sixth Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Faculty Papers (folder 3 of 3), 1993 June 6-18 (Box 35, Folder 314)
  - JCSSS - Sixth Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Evaluations, 1993 June 6-18 (Box 35, Folder 315)
  - JCSSS - Sixth Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Feedback Letters from Participants, 1993 June 6-18 (Box 35, Folder 316)
  - JCSSS - Seventh Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - General, 1994 June 5-17 (Box 35, Folder 317)
    Includes schedule and lists of faculty and participants. Also includes syllabus for Steven Solnick course on Post-Soviet Politics.
  - JCSSS - Seventh Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Applicants from the Former Soviet Union (Acceptance Letters and Declinations), 1994 June 5-17 (Box 35, Folder 318)
  - JCSSS - Seventh Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Papers, 1994 June 5-17 (Box 35, Folder 319-321)
  - JCSSS - Seventh Annual Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society - Evaluations, 1994 June 5-17 (Box 35, Folder 322)
  - JCSSS - Workshops on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Carnegie Corporation Funding, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 323)
    Grant reporting and correspondence. A Carnegie Corporation grant funded the 1993 workshop.
  - JCSSS - Workshops on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Ford Foundation Meeting, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 324)
    Discussion with Ford Foundation concerning possible funding for 1994 workshop and other projects.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Membership and Vitae, 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 325)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Correspondence and Meeting, 1983-1984 May (Box 36, Folder 326)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Correspondence and Meeting, 1984 July - 1985 (Box 36, Folder 327)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Papers and Readings, 1980-1985 (Box 36, Folder 328)
    Papers by Vera Dunham (The Worker and the Soviet System: A Literary Study) and Ed Brown ( Who Reads that Junk? Views of the Popular Culture East and West, 2 drafts); distributed at the July 1984 meeting.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Bibliography and Syllabi, 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 329)
    Includes bibliography by Jeffrey Brooks; article on the Soviet Book Market by Maurice Friedberg.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Workshop and Meeting, 1985 January (Box 36, Folder 330)
    Includes planning correspondence and minutes, 1984 October - 1985 April.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Panel at AAASS World Congress (1985), 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 331)
    American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, 3rd World Congress, Washington, DC, 1985. Correspondence concerning panel and travel arrangements.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Theatre and Muslim Popular Culture in the Soviet Union, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 332)
    Undated comments by Alma Law, Michael McLain, and James Chritchlow.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Meeting, 1986 April (Box 36, Folder 333)
    Selection meeting for Summer Seminar in Soviet Literature and Society.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Soviet Literature - Proposals, 1986 July 6-20 (Box 36, Folder 334)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Soviet Literature - Correspondence and Planning, 1986 July 6-20 (Box 36, Folder 335)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Soviet Literature - Participants, 1986 July 6-20 (Box 36, Folder 336)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Soviet Literature - Questionnaire Responses, 1986 July 6-20 (Box 37, Folder 337)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Soviet Literature - Report, 1986 July 6-20 (Box 37, Folder 338)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Meeting, 1986 October (Box 37, Folder 339)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Contemporary Soviet Culture and Society - Proposal, 1987 July 5-18 (Box 37, Folder 340)
    Literature and Film in the 1980s.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Contemporary Soviet Culture and Society - Correspondence, 1987 July 5-18 (Box 37, Folder 341)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Contemporary Soviet Culture and Society - Participants and Program, 1987 July 5-18 (Box 37, Folder 342)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Contemporary Soviet Culture and Society - Questionnaire Responses, 1987 July 5-18 (Box 37, Folder 343)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Summer Seminar in Contemporary Soviet Culture and Society - Report, 1987 July 5-18 (Box 37, Folder 344)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Meeting, 1987 September (Box 37, Folder 345-346)
    Includes materials on Soviet television; proposals concerning Popular Culture in China; and report on the 1987 Summer Seminar.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Soviet Studies in Literature Readers, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 347)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Soviet Contemporary Literature and Popular Culture Syllabi, 1984-1988 (Box 38, Folder 348)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Proposal, 1988 August 29 (Box 38, Folder 349)
    File includes an article in Russian. Proposal by Nancy Condee and Vladimir Padunov.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Planning and Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 350)
    Correspondence and report concerning the first meeting of the International Working Group, Moscow, 25-29 June 1990. Includes schedule and papers, and announcement of second meeting planned for 1991. Includes materials in Russian.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Conference Proceedings, 1990 June 25-29 (Box 38, Folder 351-352)
    In Russian. Meeting in Moscow of the International Working Group. Conference entitled, "From a Directed Culture to a Self-Developing Cultural Model."
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Project Report, 1990 September 15 (Box 38, Folder 353)
    Report on activities, April 1989 to present, and on conference in Moscow in June 1990. Includes original proposal to the JCSS for the establishment of the working group.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Meeting (Minutes), 1990 October 20 (Box 38, Folder 354)
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Meeting, 1991 June 17-21 (Box 38, Folder 355)
    International Working Group, second annual meeting, University of California, Berkeley. Includes materials in Russian.
  - JCSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Papers, 1991 June 17-21 (Box 38, Folder 356-357, Box 39, Folder 358)
    International Working Group, second annual meeting, University of California, Berkeley. Includes papers in Russian and English.
  - JCSSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 359)
    Planning for June meeting of International Working Group, Moscow. Includes materials in Russian.
  - JCSSS - Literature and Popular Culture Subcommittee - Working Group on Contemporary Soviet Culture - Papers, 1992 June 15-19 (Box 39, Folder 360-361)
    For the third annual meeting of the International Working Group, Moscow. Includes papers in Russian and in English.
  - JCSSS - Working Group on Contemporary Russian Culture - Papers, 1993 July 5-9 (Box 39, Folder 362-364)
    Fourth Meeting, London, on "Russian Culture / Soviet Hieroglyphics." Includes papers in Russian and in English.
  - JCSS - Workshop on Early East Slavic Culture - Planning and Preparation, 1987-1990 (Box 39, Folder 365)
    Includes meeting of the Working Group on Pre-Modern Russian History, January 1989.
  - JCSS - Workshop on Early East Slavic Culture - Budget and Payments, 1990 June 3-7 (Box 39, Folder 366)
  - JCSS - Workshop on Early East Slavic Culture - Report, 1990 June 3-7 (Box 39, Folder 367)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Early East Slavic Culture, 1993 June 19-24 (Box 39, Folder 368)
    Second workshop - planning, participants, and preliminary schedule. Includes notes on meeting of the Working Group on Pre-Modern Russian History, 1991 April 26-27.
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Early East Slavic Culture - Papers, 1993 June 19-24 (Box 118, Folder 1882-1885)
    Workshop at Stanford University.
  - JCSS - Sociology Subcommittee - Meetings, Memos, and Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 369)
  - JCSS - Sociology Subcommittee - Meetings, Memos, and Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 370-371)
  - JCSS - Sociology Subcommittee - Instructional Seminars, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 372)
    Reports by American sociologists on their lecture tours in the Soviet Union in June 1989.
  - JCSS - Sociology Subcommittee - Sociology Exchange Program, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 373)
    List of American and Soviet participants, and American scholars' reports on their exchange visits, 1989-1990. File also includes list of American awards for 1990-1991 and 1991-1992 years.
  - JCSS - Sociology Subcommittee - Exchange Expenditures, 1989-1990 (Box 40, Folder 374)
  - JCSS - Workshop on Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - General, 1991 July 6-14 (Box 40, Folder 375)
    First Annual Workshop on Underrepresented Fields in Soviet Studies: Sociology and Anthropology, Stanford University.
  - JCSS - Workshop on Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Papers, 1991 July 6-14 (Box 40, Folder 376-377)
  - JCSS - Workshop on Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Papers, 1991 July 6-14 (Box 41, Folder 378-379)
  - JCSS - Workshop on Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Questionnaires, 1991 July 6-14 (Box 41, Folder 380)
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - General, 1992 June 20-27 (Box 41, Folder 381)
    Second Workshop on Underrepresented Fields in Soviet Studies, Stanford University. File includes schedule, lists of participants and faculty, and participant questionnaires.
  - JCSSS - Workshop on Soviet Sociology and Anthropology - Papers, 1992 June 20-27 (Box 41, Folder 382-384)
    Second Workshop on Underrepresented Fields in Soviet Studies, Stanford University.